<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coffee on d:tour</title>
    <link>https://furycd001.github.io/tags/coffee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coffee on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:02:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://furycd001.github.io/tags/coffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Aeropress Ritual</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-aeropress-ritual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:02:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-aeropress-ritual/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the quiet stillness of the morning, before the world had fully woken, there was a moment &amp;ldquo;a ritual&amp;rdquo; that was all his own. This was his time. The sacred few minutes dedicated to crafting the perfect cup of coffee with his beloved Aeropress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kitchen was a sanctuary at this hour, bathed in the gentle light of dawn. He moved with purpose, each step a part of a dance he knew by heart. First, he reached for the coffee tub—a sturdy, reliable container that kept the grounds fresh and fragrant. As he took off the lid, a deep, earthy aroma filled the air, wrapping around him like a familiar embrace. This was a scent that spoke of warmth and comfort, with the promise of clarity to come.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sip of Adventure (part.1)</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/a-sip-of-adventure-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:03:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/a-sip-of-adventure-part-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A young girl always dreamed of a life that was big and grand, full of adventures that would take her to the far corners of the world. She believed that happiness could sometimes be found in those big adventures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hell yeah!&amp;rdquo; she shouted one morning, pouring a delicious mug of steaming hot coffee. The rich aroma filled her small kitchen, and for a moment, the world seemed perfect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Oh, hell yeah!&amp;rdquo; she exclaimed again, sitting down in her comfy chair by the window. Taking her first sip of the delicious brew, she felt a warmth spread through her, not just from the coffee, but from the excitement of possibility.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morning Emma</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/morning-emma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:54:02 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/morning-emma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every morning, Emma woke up with a smile, not because of the day&amp;rsquo;s prospects but because of the joy that awaited her in the kitchen. Her mornings began with a ritual she cherished above all else: making and enjoying her perfect cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She would shuffle out of bed, her slippers softly padding across the floor, and head straight to the kitchen. The familiar sight of her beloved coffee maker greeted her like an old friend. Emma loved the routine of preparing her coffee. She took out the fresh beans she&amp;rsquo;d bought from a local roaster, their rich, earthy aroma already starting to awaken her senses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Joys of Joe</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-joys-of-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:40:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-joys-of-joe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every morning, the kitchen came to life with the anticipation of a special ritual: the making of a perfect cup of coffee. As dawn&amp;rsquo;s first light filtered through the window, the beans awaited their transformation from mere ingredients into a steamy cup of joe, brimming with joy, promise, and excitement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The journey began by selecting the beans, and carefully measuring them. Each bean holding the potential for greatness, ready to release its essence. The grinder whirred to life, breaking the beans into a fragrant pile of grounds, a prelude to the symphony of flavours about to unfold.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Early Days of Paid Wifi With Starbucks</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-early-days-of-paid-wifi-with-starbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:18:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-early-days-of-paid-wifi-with-starbucks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the late 2000s, Starbucks emerged as more than just a coffee haven; it became a social hub, a place to connect with friends and colleagues. However, during this period, the concept of free WiFi was not as ubiquitous as it is today. Instead, Starbucks UK offered a WiFi experience that required payment for access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-era-of-paid-wifi-at-starbucks-uk&#34;&gt;The Era of Paid WiFi at Starbucks UK..&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Around 2006 and 2007, Starbucks introduced its WiFi service to stores across the UK &amp;amp; Ireland, offering customers the opportunity to access the internet while sipping their favorite beverages. However, unlike today’s widespread availability of free WiFi at various establishments, the service came with a nominal fee.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
