<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Linux on d:tour</title>
    <link>https://furycd001.github.io/tags/linux/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Linux on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:32:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://furycd001.github.io/tags/linux/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why a Derivative of a Derivative Might Not Be the Best Choice</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/derivative-of-a-derivative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/derivative-of-a-derivative/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to choosing a Linux distribution, the options can feel overwhelming. From the giants like Arch, Fedora, OpenSuse and Ubuntu, to the more niche derivatives that branch off these powerhouses, there’s a flavor for just about everyone. But what happens when you venture beyond a first-layer derivative to a derivative of a derivative? While it might seem harmless, this extra step away from the “source” can sometimes create unforeseen challenges that are worth considering before you commit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Creating an Interactive Bash Script</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/basics-of-creating-an-interactive-bash-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 10:49:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/basics-of-creating-an-interactive-bash-script/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creating an interactive bash script is like adding a dash of magic to your terminal adventures!! It’s a fun and clever way to automate repetitive tasks and make your command-line experience smoother and more enjoyable. Here’s a little guide to sprinkle some scripting sparkle into your life:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;create-the-script-file&#34;&gt;Create the Script File:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Start by creating a new file for your script. Open your terminal and use a text editor to create a file, such as &lt;code&gt;vim script-whatever.sh&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining Terminal Software</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/reimagining-terminal-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/reimagining-terminal-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the world of technology, there’s something quietly beautiful about the way people are revisiting and reimagining old terminal software. These programs, with their roots dating back to the early days of computing, have been the backbone of countless systems for decades. But as technology evolves, so do the ways we interact with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some modern developers are taking these time-tested tools and giving them a fresh coat of paint, not to erase the past but to enhance it. By rewriting and tweaking the old software, they aim to improve functionality, make interfaces more intuitive, or simply adapt the software to meet today’s needs. It’s a delicate balance—respecting the original while embracing the possibilities of the new.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Joy in Linux: Why It’s My Happy Place</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:32:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s something truly special about finding something that not only fits your needs but also brings you joy. For me, that&amp;rsquo;s Linux. It’s more than just an operating system—it’s a source of happiness, freedom, and all things good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using Linux since 2002, and I can honestly say I’ve never looked back. There’s a certain magic in its flexibility and the way it empowers you to customize everything just the way you like. Unlike Windows or macOS, Linux doesn’t box you in; instead, it opens up a world of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
