<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joe on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/joe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joe on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:40:40 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/joe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Morning Coffee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/morning-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 07:40:40 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/morning-coffee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The kitchen was small. Not in a sad way, more like a cozy way, like it had decided long ago it didn’t need to impress anyone. The cabinets were slightly crooked, the window rattled when the wind got opinionated, and the old radiator made ticking sounds like it was keeping score. But in the soft, amber light of a the morning, the space felt almost enchanted, like it knew how to hold quiet moments just right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Quiet Joy of That First Morning Joe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-quiet-joy-of-that-first-morning-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 06:59:25 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-quiet-joy-of-that-first-morning-joe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s a sacred stillness to the early hours. Before the world stirs, before notifications blink to life, and before the rush begins, there exists a space of serenity that asks nothing of us but to simply be. It’s in that quiet, often overlooked moment that we find one of life’s purest joys: the first sip of morning coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The warmth of the cup in your hands. The gentle steam rising like whispers into the silence. The first deep breath of that rich aroma, it’s more than caffeine. It’s a ritual of presence. A gentle grounding. A reminder that before we chase the day, we are allowed this pause.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Aeropress Ritual</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-aeropress-ritual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:02:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-aeropress-ritual/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the quiet stillness of the morning, before the world had fully woken, there was a moment &amp;ldquo;a ritual&amp;rdquo; that was all his own. This was his time. The sacred few minutes dedicated to crafting the perfect cup of coffee with his beloved Aeropress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kitchen was a sanctuary at this hour, bathed in the gentle light of dawn. He moved with purpose, each step a part of a dance he knew by heart. First, he reached for the coffee tub—a sturdy, reliable container that kept the grounds fresh and fragrant. As he took off the lid, a deep, earthy aroma filled the air, wrapping around him like a familiar embrace. This was a scent that spoke of warmth and comfort, with the promise of clarity to come.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morning Emma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/morning-emma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:54:02 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/morning-emma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every morning, Emma woke up with a smile, not because of the day&amp;rsquo;s prospects but because of the joy that awaited her in the kitchen. Her mornings began with a ritual she cherished above all else: making and enjoying her perfect cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She would shuffle out of bed, her slippers softly padding across the floor, and head straight to the kitchen. The familiar sight of her beloved coffee maker greeted her like an old friend. Emma loved the routine of preparing her coffee. She took out the fresh beans she&amp;rsquo;d bought from a local roaster, their rich, earthy aroma already starting to awaken her senses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Joys of Joe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-joys-of-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:40:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-joys-of-joe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every morning, the kitchen came to life with the anticipation of a special ritual: the making of a perfect cup of coffee. As dawn&amp;rsquo;s first light filtered through the window, the beans awaited their transformation from mere ingredients into a steamy cup of joe, brimming with joy, promise, and excitement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The journey began by selecting the beans, and carefully measuring them. Each bean holding the potential for greatness, ready to release its essence. The grinder whirred to life, breaking the beans into a fragrant pile of grounds, a prelude to the symphony of flavours about to unfold.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
