<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Joy on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/joy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Joy on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:02:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/joy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Aeropress Ritual</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-aeropress-ritual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:02:42 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-aeropress-ritual/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the quiet stillness of the morning, before the world had fully woken, there was a moment &amp;ldquo;a ritual&amp;rdquo; that was all his own. This was his time. The sacred few minutes dedicated to crafting the perfect cup of coffee with his beloved Aeropress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kitchen was a sanctuary at this hour, bathed in the gentle light of dawn. He moved with purpose, each step a part of a dance he knew by heart. First, he reached for the coffee tub—a sturdy, reliable container that kept the grounds fresh and fragrant. As he took off the lid, a deep, earthy aroma filled the air, wrapping around him like a familiar embrace. This was a scent that spoke of warmth and comfort, with the promise of clarity to come.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Joy in Linux: Why It’s My Happy Place</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:32:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s something truly special about finding something that not only fits your needs but also brings you joy. For me, that&amp;rsquo;s Linux. It’s more than just an operating system—it’s a source of happiness, freedom, and all things good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using Linux since 2002, and I can honestly say I’ve never looked back. There’s a certain magic in its flexibility and the way it empowers you to customize everything just the way you like. Unlike Windows or macOS, Linux doesn’t box you in; instead, it opens up a world of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morning Emma</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/morning-emma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:54:02 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/morning-emma/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every morning, Emma woke up with a smile, not because of the day&amp;rsquo;s prospects but because of the joy that awaited her in the kitchen. Her mornings began with a ritual she cherished above all else: making and enjoying her perfect cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She would shuffle out of bed, her slippers softly padding across the floor, and head straight to the kitchen. The familiar sight of her beloved coffee maker greeted her like an old friend. Emma loved the routine of preparing her coffee. She took out the fresh beans she&amp;rsquo;d bought from a local roaster, their rich, earthy aroma already starting to awaken her senses.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Joys of Joe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-joys-of-joe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:40:59 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-joys-of-joe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Every morning, the kitchen came to life with the anticipation of a special ritual: the making of a perfect cup of coffee. As dawn&amp;rsquo;s first light filtered through the window, the beans awaited their transformation from mere ingredients into a steamy cup of joe, brimming with joy, promise, and excitement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The journey began by selecting the beans, and carefully measuring them. Each bean holding the potential for greatness, ready to release its essence. The grinder whirred to life, breaking the beans into a fragrant pile of grounds, a prelude to the symphony of flavours about to unfold.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
