<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:17:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Always Have a Sense of Your Own Ridiculousness</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/always-have-a-sense-of-your-own-ridiculousness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 08:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/always-have-a-sense-of-your-own-ridiculousness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s something magical about letting life surprise you with its absurdity. When we talk about having a sense of your own ridiculousness, it’s not about self-deprecation or undermining your worth. No, it’s about celebrating the quirks, the little missteps, and the delightful messiness that make you unapologetically you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Life is a canvas splattered with imperfections—smudges, unexpected colors, and strokes that went a little off course. Those &amp;ldquo;mistakes&amp;rdquo;? They’re what make the painting captivating. A sense of your own ridiculousness means learning to laugh at yourself, to find joy in the absurd moments, and to embrace the unique art you’re creating every day.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Space - The Sweet Art of Slowing Down</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/white-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 08:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/white-space/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The noise is getting noisier. The distractions? Louder than ever. These days, it feels like we&amp;rsquo;re all rushing to keep up—plugged in, switched on, and racing through life at full throttle. Diaries packed, to-do lists overflowing, and a constant stream of &amp;ldquo;urgent&amp;rdquo; demands knocking at our doors. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder the world feels a bit overwhelming sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But have you noticed something curious? When the rare moments of peace and quiet finally come, we often don’t know what to do with them. We&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten how to simply be. We’ve lost touch with the beautiful necessity of white space—the calm moments in life that allow us to breathe, reflect, and restore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Gleno Northern Ireland</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-brief-history-of-gleno-northern-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 07:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-brief-history-of-gleno-northern-ireland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nestled in the picturesque landscapes of County Antrim, Northern Ireland, the small village of Gleno is often overlooked by visitors, yet its charm and history make it a fascinating stop for those seeking to explore Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s rich heritage. Though small in size, Gleno is a village steeped in local lore, natural beauty, and historical significance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;origins-and-name&#34;&gt;Origins and Name&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The name &lt;em&gt;Gleno&lt;/em&gt;, or &lt;em&gt;Glenoe&lt;/em&gt;, is derived from the Irish &lt;em&gt;Gleann Ó&lt;/em&gt;, meaning &amp;ldquo;Glen of the mass or lump.&amp;rdquo; This name reflects the unique geological features of the area, including the prominent hills and rock formations that frame the village. Located in County Antrim, Gleno is located near a scenic waterfall that feeds into a meandering stream, a feature that has shaped much of its early history, and has attracted settlement for centuries due to its scenic beauty and the life-giving stream that flows through the valley. Gleno&amp;rsquo;s tranquil surroundings, characterized by rolling hills and lush greenery, have made it an attractive spot for human settlement for centuries, with roots stretching back to early farming communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falling Apart</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/falling-apart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 09:58:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/falling-apart/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, it feels like we&amp;rsquo;re falling apart, like no matter what we do, we&amp;rsquo;re always falling short, making mistakes, messing things up, or that something goes wrong. But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: we&amp;rsquo;re not always any of those things. Life can simply be hard sometimes. It&amp;rsquo;s full of challenges, unexpected twists, and moments that can make us feel overwhelmed or that the weight of the world is too much to carry. There are days when it seems like giving up might be easier than pushing forward. Just sometimes, life is simply hard.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spreading Kindness Online: Creating a Ripple Effect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/spreading-kindness-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/spreading-kindness-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the digital age, the internet has become a central part of our daily lives. It&amp;rsquo;s a place where we connect with friends, share our thoughts, and discover new ideas. However, it&amp;rsquo;s also a space that can sometimes feel overwhelming and negative. Amidst the noise, a simple yet powerful truth remains: kindness online can have a ripple effect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine this.. You receive a heartfelt comment on a post you shared, or someone sends you an encouraging message when you need it most. These small acts of kindness can brighten your day and change your outlook. The beauty of kindness is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop with you. One small act of kindness can inspire others to follow suit, creating a wave of positivity that can spread far and wide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Depression of the Internet: Pulling Us Away from Real Life</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-depression-of-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:41:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-depression-of-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the digital age, the internet has become an integral part of our daily lives. It connects us to a world of information, entertainment, and social interaction. Yet, as we immerse ourselves in this vast virtual landscape, there is a growing concern about the impact it has on our mental health and our connection to real life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-allure-of-the-digital-world&#34;&gt;The Allure of the Digital World&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The internet offers endless possibilities. From social media platforms to streaming services, online shopping to gaming, it provides an escape from the mundane and a distraction from the stresses of everyday life. However, this constant accessibility and the allure of instant gratification can also lead to a dangerous cycle of overuse and dependency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
