<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 23:17:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mindful Tech: Embracing Life With an Older Android Phone</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/mindful-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 23:17:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/mindful-tech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a world that constantly pushes us toward the newest devices and the fastest updates, there is a quiet satisfaction in choosing to continue using what we already have, especially when it comes to our smartphones. If you are still using an older Android phone beyond its official warranty and support period, you are not alone. You are also not wrong to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a certain mindfulness that comes with this decision. It invites us to be more aware, more deliberate, and more intentional. This applies not just to our tech, but also to our habits and our overall digital hygiene.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a System Service Manager: A Personal Perspective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/system-service-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:25:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/system-service-managers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to system service managers on Linux, such as systemd, OpenRC, runit, SysVinit, and others, the conversation can quickly turn into a debate. Each has its merits, its history, and its dedicated user base. But for most people using Linux on a desktop or laptop, the differences between them often fade quietly into the background.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At their core, service managers are responsible for initializing the system, managing background services (daemons), handling dependencies, logging, and shutting down gracefully. On servers, where stability, fine-grained control, and predictability are essential, choosing the right init system can be a high-stakes decision. Administrators often require transparency, auditability, and exact behavior, especially in high-availability or containerized environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Derivative of a Derivative Might Not Be the Best Choice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/derivative-of-a-derivative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/derivative-of-a-derivative/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to choosing a Linux distribution, the options can feel overwhelming. From the giants like Arch, Fedora, OpenSuse and Ubuntu, to the more niche derivatives that branch off these powerhouses, there’s a flavor for just about everyone. But what happens when you venture beyond a first-layer derivative to a derivative of a derivative? While it might seem harmless, this extra step away from the “source” can sometimes create unforeseen challenges that are worth considering before you commit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining Terminal Software</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/reimagining-terminal-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/reimagining-terminal-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the world of technology, there’s something quietly beautiful about the way people are revisiting and reimagining old terminal software. These programs, with their roots dating back to the early days of computing, have been the backbone of countless systems for decades. But as technology evolves, so do the ways we interact with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some modern developers are taking these time-tested tools and giving them a fresh coat of paint, not to erase the past but to enhance it. By rewriting and tweaking the old software, they aim to improve functionality, make interfaces more intuitive, or simply adapt the software to meet today’s needs. It’s a delicate balance—respecting the original while embracing the possibilities of the new.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Joy in Linux: Why It’s My Happy Place</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:32:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There’s something truly special about finding something that not only fits your needs but also brings you joy. For me, that&amp;rsquo;s Linux. It’s more than just an operating system—it’s a source of happiness, freedom, and all things good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been using Linux since 2002, and I can honestly say I’ve never looked back. There’s a certain magic in its flexibility and the way it empowers you to customize everything just the way you like. Unlike Windows or macOS, Linux doesn’t box you in; instead, it opens up a world of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Minimalism on Modern Day Smartphones</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/embracing-minimalism-on-modern-day-smartphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/embracing-minimalism-on-modern-day-smartphones/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In our fast-paced digital age, smartphones have become indispensable companions, seamlessly integrating into our daily lives. However, as these devices grow more advanced, they often come laden with features and apps that can lead to a cluttered and overwhelming experience. For some it can also be an undesirable experience. Enter minimalism—a philosophy that, when applied to modern smartphones, can bring clarity and purpose back to our digital interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Minimalism on smartphones can take many forms, but for me, it&amp;rsquo;s all about decluttering and simplifying. It&amp;rsquo;s about curating an environment that encourages focus and productivity rather than distraction. I keep what matters within reach while removing the unwanted or unneeded. I start by evaluating the apps on my home screen: are they essential, a one-time use, or just there because I downloaded them and never removed them? Removing redundant or unused apps can immediately make your phone feel less chaotic. Additionally, consider the widgets that consume your home screen. Keep only those that provide valuable information, helping you stay organized without overwhelming your visual space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pc Perdicaments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pc-perdicaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:55:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pc-perdicaments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a cosy kitchen, a computer sat quietly in the corner underneath a black wooden desk. A reliable companion in a world increasingly dominated by sleek, modern devices. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t old, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t brand new either—a comfortable middle ground. Running Linux, it represented a blend of stability and versatility, though not without its quirks. Its owner didn’t ask for much—just for it to work as expected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every morning, the computer was powered on with a sense of hope. The familiar hum of the fan and the soft glow of the screen brought a small but significant comfort. Its operating system, a sturdy version of Linux, booted up smoothly most days. However, there were times when unexpected glitches would appear—a program crashing here, a slow response there. These minor annoyances didn’t make the computer boring; they added a layer of challenge, a puzzle to solve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
