<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on d:tour</title>
    <link>https://furycd001.github.io/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 06:54:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://furycd001.github.io/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining Terminal Software</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/reimagining-terminal-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 06:54:17 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/reimagining-terminal-software/</guid>
      <description>In the world of technology, there’s something quietly beautiful about the way people are revisiting and reimagining old terminal software. These programs, with their roots dating back to the early days of computing, have been the backbone of countless systems for decades. But as technology evolves, so do the ways we interact with it.&#xA;Some modern developers are taking these time-tested tools and giving them a fresh coat of paint, not to erase the past but to enhance it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Joy in Linux: Why It’s My Happy Place</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 06:32:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/finding-joy-in-linux/</guid>
      <description>There’s something truly special about finding something that not only fits your needs but also brings you joy. For me, that&amp;rsquo;s Linux. It’s more than just an operating system—it’s a source of happiness, freedom, and all things good.&#xA;I’ve been using Linux since 2002, and I can honestly say I’ve never looked back. There’s a certain magic in its flexibility and the way it empowers you to customize everything just the way you like.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Minimalism on Modern Day Smartphones</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/embracing-minimalism-on-modern-day-smartphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/embracing-minimalism-on-modern-day-smartphones/</guid>
      <description>In our fast-paced digital age, smartphones have become indispensable companions, seamlessly integrating into our daily lives. However, as these devices grow more advanced, they often come laden with features and apps that can lead to a cluttered and overwhelming experience. For some it can also be an undesirable experience. Enter minimalism—a philosophy that, when applied to modern smartphones, can bring clarity and purpose back to our digital interactions.&#xA;Minimalism on smartphones can take many forms, but for me, it&amp;rsquo;s all about decluttering and simplifying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pc Perdicaments</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/pc-perdicaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:55:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/pc-perdicaments/</guid>
      <description>In a cosy kitchen, a computer sat quietly in the corner underneath a black wooden desk. A reliable companion in a world increasingly dominated by sleek, modern devices. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t old, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t brand new either—a comfortable middle ground. Running Linux, it represented a blend of stability and versatility, though not without its quirks. Its owner didn’t ask for much—just for it to work as expected.&#xA;Every morning, the computer was powered on with a sense of hope.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
