<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dream on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/dream/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dream on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:37:32 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/dream/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Life as a Dream: The Imagination of Ourselves</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/life-as-a-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:37:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/life-as-a-dream/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Life is only a dream, and we are the imagination of ourselves.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, this phrase sounds poetic, almost surreal. But within it lies a profound perspective on existence, one that challenges how we perceive reality, identity, and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If life is a dream, then what we call “reality” may be less solid than we think. Perception filters our experiences, memories, and beliefs, shaping them through thoughts, feelings, and stories we tell ourselves. What we think of as &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo; is not fixed but fluid, a narrative continually written and rewritten in the mind&amp;rsquo;s theater.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clumsy Footsteps to Stardom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/clumsy-footsteps-to-stardom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:34:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/clumsy-footsteps-to-stardom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a quaint little town, there lived a girl named Mia who had a dream. She wanted nothing more than to become a tap dancer, her feet creating rhythms that would captivate audiences. However, there was a small problem: Mia had no rhythm, was always out of balance, and was extremely clumsy. Despite her shortcomings, Mia&amp;rsquo;s heart was set on her dream, and she practiced tirelessly, day after day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No matter how hard she tried, Mia seemed to get nowhere. Her tap shoes tripped her up, and her feet seemed to have a mind of their own. Yet, she never gave up. Her determination caught the attention of a local theater director who was putting together a small-town comedy show. Seeing potential in her comedic clumsiness, he offered her a small role.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
