<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Minimalist on d:tour</title>
    <link>https://furycd001.github.io/tags/minimalist/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Minimalist on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 23:17:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://furycd001.github.io/tags/minimalist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mindful Tech: Embracing Life With an Older Android Phone</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/mindful-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 23:17:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/mindful-tech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a world that constantly pushes us toward the newest devices and the fastest updates, there is a quiet satisfaction in choosing to continue using what we already have, especially when it comes to our smartphones. If you are still using an older Android phone beyond its official warranty and support period, you are not alone. You are also not wrong to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a certain mindfulness that comes with this decision. It invites us to be more aware, more deliberate, and more intentional. This applies not just to our tech, but also to our habits and our overall digital hygiene.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimalism in Love</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/minimalism-in-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 07:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/minimalism-in-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Minimalism is a mindset, a way of simplifying life, focusing on what truly matters, and letting go of distractions. I’ve embraced this philosophy, striving for a life unburdened by excess and filled with a clear mind. Yet, minimalism isn’t just about things; it’s about relationships too. And that&amp;rsquo;s where I find my greatest lesson in balance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You see, I share my life with someone who loves ornaments, picture frames, wall art, and all the little things that bring her joy. Our home is filled with the warmth of her personality: colorful, sentimental, and alive. It’s a stark contrast to the minimalist ideal I sometimes yearn for, serene, uncluttered, and bare. There have been moments when I wished it would all vanish, that the house could mirror the simplicity I find calming. And then there are times when I simply ignore it, focusing on quietness.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mindful Bookmarking</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/mindful-firefox-bookmarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 10:12:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/mindful-firefox-bookmarks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to accumulate a cluttered and overwhelming collection of bookmarks in your web browser. A disorganized bookmark list can make it difficult to find what you need and can contribute to digital overwhelm. By organizing your browsers bookmarks thoughtfully, you can create a more mindful and efficient browsing experience.  To achieve this, you can consider following a series of thoughtful and carefully planned steps..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-audit-your-current-bookmarks&#34;&gt;1. Audit Your Current Bookmarks&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review and Clean:&lt;/strong&gt; Start by reviewing all your existing bookmarks. Delete any that are outdated, irrelevant, or ones that may no longer serve a purpos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Minimalism on Modern Day Smartphones</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/embracing-minimalism-on-modern-day-smartphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 07:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/embracing-minimalism-on-modern-day-smartphones/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In our fast-paced digital age, smartphones have become indispensable companions, seamlessly integrating into our daily lives. However, as these devices grow more advanced, they often come laden with features and apps that can lead to a cluttered and overwhelming experience. For some it can also be an undesirable experience. Enter minimalism—a philosophy that, when applied to modern smartphones, can bring clarity and purpose back to our digital interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Minimalism on smartphones can take many forms, but for me, it&amp;rsquo;s all about decluttering and simplifying. It&amp;rsquo;s about curating an environment that encourages focus and productivity rather than distraction. I keep what matters within reach while removing the unwanted or unneeded. I start by evaluating the apps on my home screen: are they essential, a one-time use, or just there because I downloaded them and never removed them? Removing redundant or unused apps can immediately make your phone feel less chaotic. Additionally, consider the widgets that consume your home screen. Keep only those that provide valuable information, helping you stay organized without overwhelming your visual space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Harmony of Minimalism</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-harmony-of-minimalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 06:59:52 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-harmony-of-minimalism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Living with a minimalist mindset can be a serene and liberating experience. It’s about embracing simplicity and finding joy in the essentials, creating a sanctuary of calm in a world that often feels overwhelming. Yet, what happens when minimalism shares a space with a bit of delightful clutter?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine a home where clean, open spaces coexist with charming knick-knacks and treasured collections. Here, minimalism and a more eclectic approach dance together in a harmonious waltz, each step complementing the other. This unique blend creates a living environment that is both functional and full of personality.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pc Perdicaments</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/pc-perdicaments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 09:55:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/pc-perdicaments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a cosy kitchen, a computer sat quietly in the corner underneath a black wooden desk. A reliable companion in a world increasingly dominated by sleek, modern devices. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t old, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t brand new either—a comfortable middle ground. Running Linux, it represented a blend of stability and versatility, though not without its quirks. Its owner didn’t ask for much—just for it to work as expected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every morning, the computer was powered on with a sense of hope. The familiar hum of the fan and the soft glow of the screen brought a small but significant comfort. Its operating system, a sturdy version of Linux, booted up smoothly most days. However, there were times when unexpected glitches would appear—a program crashing here, a slow response there. These minor annoyances didn’t make the computer boring; they added a layer of challenge, a puzzle to solve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
