<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:34:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Clumsy Footsteps to Stardom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/clumsy-footsteps-to-stardom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:34:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/clumsy-footsteps-to-stardom/</guid>
      <description>In a quaint little town, there lived a girl named Mia who had a dream. She wanted nothing more than to become a tap dancer, her feet creating rhythms that would captivate audiences. However, there was a small problem: Mia had no rhythm, was always out of balance, and was extremely clumsy. Despite her shortcomings, Mia&amp;rsquo;s heart was set on her dream, and she practiced tirelessly, day after day.&#xA;No matter how hard she tried, Mia seemed to get nowhere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unforgettable Picnic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-unforgettable-picnic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 07:17:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-unforgettable-picnic/</guid>
      <description>In a peaceful meadow nestled between rolling hills, a group of friendly animals decided to have a delightful picnic. The sun was shining, the birds were singing, and the scent of wildflowers filled the air. It was the perfect day for a gathering of friends. Among them were Benny the Bear, Lucy the Rabbit, Max the Squirrel, and Andy the Ant Eater.&#xA;They arrived at their favorite spot under the big oak tree, setting down a colorful blanket and unpacking baskets full of delicious treats.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obsession</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/obsession/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:11:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/obsession/</guid>
      <description>In the heart of a quaint little town, nestled among rolling hills and whispering trees, there lived a young woman named Lily. Lily was a dreamer, her mind often lost in the mysteries of the universe. She found solace in the unseen, the intangible, and the inexplicable.&#xA;One crisp autumn evening, as the moon cast its gentle glow upon the world, Lily found herself lost in contemplation. What could she do with her obsession, she wondered, with the things she could not see?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cruz and the Mud Puddle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cruz-and-the-mud-puddle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:43:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cruz-and-the-mud-puddle/</guid>
      <description>In the heart of the sprawling wilderness, there lived a charming bulldog named Cruz. Cruz was no ordinary bulldog; he was an intrepid explorer with a heart full of adventure. He traveled the country in a cozy, colorful van with his owner, Chrome. Chrome was a free spirit with a love for the open road, and together, they explored every nook and cranny of the beautiful landscape.&#xA;One crisp morning, Cruz and Chrome arrived at a picturesque campground nestled among towering pine trees and shimmering lakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chromes Fruity Fiasco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chromes-fruity-fiasco/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:02:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chromes-fruity-fiasco/</guid>
      <description>Chrome wandered through the bustling market, eyeing the vibrant display of fruit. He picked up a ripe mango, its sweet aroma mingling with the scent of nearby oranges and strawberries. As he bit into the juicy flesh, Chrome couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but smile, savoring the burst of tropical flavor that transported him to a sunny paradise.&#xA;Chrome tripped over a rogue pineapple and landed face-first in a pile of watermelons. &amp;ldquo;Well, at least I&amp;rsquo;m getting my daily fruit intake,&amp;rdquo; he muttered, spitting out seeds and trying to regain his dignity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Early Days of Paid Wifi With Strbucks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-early-days-of-paid-wifi-with-strbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:18:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-early-days-of-paid-wifi-with-strbucks/</guid>
      <description>In the late 2000s, Starbucks emerged as more than just a coffee haven; it became a social hub, a place to connect with friends and colleagues. However, during this period, the concept of free WiFi was not as ubiquitous as it is today. Instead, Starbucks UK offered a WiFi experience that required payment for access.&#xA;The Era of Paid WiFi at Starbucks UK.. Around 2006 and 2007, Starbucks introduced its WiFi service to stores across the UK &amp;amp; Ireland, offering customers the opportunity to access the internet while sipping their favorite beverages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ideas, thoughts, &amp; ramblings.....</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ideas-and-ramblings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 08:16:35 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ideas-and-ramblings/</guid>
      <description>Ideas, thoughts &amp;amp; Ramblings&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s what this blog is all about. After spending a few days playing around with Hugo offline, I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that I actually quite like it. It&amp;rsquo;s like a refreshing change.&#xA;A Fresh Start.. Initially, my plan was to transfer all my old blog posts from Publii to this new blog. However, upon reflection, I decided against it. A few of those posts were of low quality, and frankly, I have no idea why I ever published them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 10:20:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-blog/</guid>
      <description>After using publii for several years, I&amp;rsquo;ve finally decided to switch to Hugo. I made the switch because I wanted a more minimalistic, less clunky, and easier-to-maintain solution.&#xA;At the moment, I&amp;rsquo;m just testing Hugo, and this post is primarily for experimental purposes. After re-uploading a few posts from my previous blog, I&amp;rsquo;ll look at my feelings towards Hugo based on my experience and the results. Depending on how I feel about it, I may or may not stick with Hugo.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
