<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Internet on d:tour</title>
    <link>https://furycd001.github.io/tags/internet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Internet on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:19:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://furycd001.github.io/tags/internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Web Wasnt Built for Age Gates</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-web-wasnt-built-for-age-gates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:19:29 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-web-wasnt-built-for-age-gates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent years, we’ve watched the web, once a messy, wild, gloriously chaotic frontier, be slowly strangled under the guise of “safety.” Of all the regulatory assaults on the open internet, few are more deceptive, misguided, and insidiously destructive than &lt;em&gt;age verification&lt;/em&gt; (AV). These mandates, imposed by governments in a growing number of countries, force websites to demand deeply personal user data like ID documents, facial scans, and credit card info just to access legal content. And what do we get in return? A false sense of security, a broken internet, and a chilling step toward mass surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spreading Kindness Online: Creating a Ripple Effect</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/spreading-kindness-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/spreading-kindness-online/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the digital age, the internet has become a central part of our daily lives. It&amp;rsquo;s a place where we connect with friends, share our thoughts, and discover new ideas. However, it&amp;rsquo;s also a space that can sometimes feel overwhelming and negative. Amidst the noise, a simple yet powerful truth remains: kindness online can have a ripple effect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine this.. You receive a heartfelt comment on a post you shared, or someone sends you an encouraging message when you need it most. These small acts of kindness can brighten your day and change your outlook. The beauty of kindness is that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t stop with you. One small act of kindness can inspire others to follow suit, creating a wave of positivity that can spread far and wide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Depression of the Internet: Pulling Us Away from Real Life</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-depression-of-the-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 11:41:27 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-depression-of-the-internet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the digital age, the internet has become an integral part of our daily lives. It connects us to a world of information, entertainment, and social interaction. Yet, as we immerse ourselves in this vast virtual landscape, there is a growing concern about the impact it has on our mental health and our connection to real life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-allure-of-the-digital-world&#34;&gt;The Allure of the Digital World&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The internet offers endless possibilities. From social media platforms to streaming services, online shopping to gaming, it provides an escape from the mundane and a distraction from the stresses of everyday life. However, this constant accessibility and the allure of instant gratification can also lead to a dangerous cycle of overuse and dependency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Early Days of Paid Wifi With Starbucks</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-early-days-of-paid-wifi-with-starbucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:18:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/the-early-days-of-paid-wifi-with-starbucks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the late 2000s, Starbucks emerged as more than just a coffee haven; it became a social hub, a place to connect with friends and colleagues. However, during this period, the concept of free WiFi was not as ubiquitous as it is today. Instead, Starbucks UK offered a WiFi experience that required payment for access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-era-of-paid-wifi-at-starbucks-uk&#34;&gt;The Era of Paid WiFi at Starbucks UK..&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Around 2006 and 2007, Starbucks introduced its WiFi service to stores across the UK &amp;amp; Ireland, offering customers the opportunity to access the internet while sipping their favorite beverages. However, unlike today’s widespread availability of free WiFi at various establishments, the service came with a nominal fee.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
