<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mindfulness on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/mindfulness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mindfulness on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 20:56:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/mindfulness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Embracing the power of silence: A somewhat guide to mindful living</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/embracing-the-power-of-silence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 20:56:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/embracing-the-power-of-silence/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In a world that often feels overwhelmingly noisy, taking time to be still and speak less can have a profound impact on our wellbeing. Mindfulness isn&amp;rsquo;t just about meditation or quiet reflection—it&amp;rsquo;s about cultivating a lifestyle that values listening over constant chatter, intentionality over impulsiveness, and inner calm over external chaos. In this post, I want to try and explore the benefits of embracing silence and offer some practical tips for integrating more mindful moments into your daily.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Space - The Sweet Art of Slowing Down</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/white-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 08:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/white-space/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The noise is getting noisier. The distractions? Louder than ever. These days, it feels like we&amp;rsquo;re all rushing to keep up—plugged in, switched on, and racing through life at full throttle. Diaries packed, to-do lists overflowing, and a constant stream of &amp;ldquo;urgent&amp;rdquo; demands knocking at our doors. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder the world feels a bit overwhelming sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But have you noticed something curious? When the rare moments of peace and quiet finally come, we often don’t know what to do with them. We&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten how to simply be. We’ve lost touch with the beautiful necessity of white space—the calm moments in life that allow us to breathe, reflect, and restore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
