<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PauseAndBreathe on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/pauseandbreathe/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PauseAndBreathe on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:37:32 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/pauseandbreathe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Life as a Dream: The Imagination of Ourselves</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/life-as-a-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:37:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/life-as-a-dream/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Life is only a dream, and we are the imagination of ourselves.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, this phrase sounds poetic—almost surreal. But within it lies a profound perspective on existence, one that challenges how we perceive reality, identity, and purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If life is a dream, then what we call “reality” may be less solid than we think. Our experiences, memories, beliefs—they&amp;rsquo;re all filtered through perception, shaped by thoughts, feelings, and stories we tell ourselves. What we think of as &amp;ldquo;me&amp;rdquo; is not fixed, but fluid—a narrative continually written and rewritten in the mind&amp;rsquo;s theater.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Space - The Sweet Art of Slowing Down</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/white-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 08:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/white-space/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The noise is getting noisier. The distractions? Louder than ever. These days, it feels like we&amp;rsquo;re all rushing to keep up—plugged in, switched on, and racing through life at full throttle. Diaries packed, to-do lists overflowing, and a constant stream of &amp;ldquo;urgent&amp;rdquo; demands knocking at our doors. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder the world feels a bit overwhelming sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But have you noticed something curious? When the rare moments of peace and quiet finally come, we often don’t know what to do with them. We&amp;rsquo;ve forgotten how to simply be. We’ve lost touch with the beautiful necessity of white space—the calm moments in life that allow us to breathe, reflect, and restore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
