<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operating Systems on d:tour</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/operating-systems/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operating Systems on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:53:47 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/operating-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Transition From X11 to wayland</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-transition-from-x11-to-wayland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 06:53:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-transition-from-x11-to-wayland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, Linux desktops have used X11 (via X.Org Server) to render windows and manage input. wayland emerged as a modern, simpler, and more secure protocol, with compositors like GNOME’s Mutter, KDE’s KWin, Sway, Weston, and others implementing it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yet most existing applications, and many workflows, rely on X11. That’s why Xwayland was created, to serve as a bridge that allows X11 applications to function within a wayland environment. It translates X protocol requests into wayland-compatible ones, allowing legacy applications to continue running, often with little to no disruption.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Refuse to Use Electron Apps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-i-refuse-to-use-electron-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 08:55:11 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/why-i-refuse-to-use-electron-apps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve made a conscious decision to avoid Electron-based applications like Discord and Spotify. This stems from the same philosophy that guides me away from many popular browsers: a preference for efficiency, simplicity, and respect for system resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Electron apps bundle an entire instance of the Chromium web engine with every application. In effect, each one is running its own standalone browser, just to render what could otherwise be a lightweight interface. This design choice might be convenient for developers, but it comes at a significant cost to users: increased RAM and CPU usage, larger disk footprints, and slower performance, especially noticeable on older or less powerful machines. There&amp;rsquo;s also the added concern of security, since these apps often lag behind in updating the embedded Chromium engine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dive into DistroSea..</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/dive-into-distrosea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 07:46:58 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/dive-into-distrosea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wanted to explore a Linux distribution without the fuss of downloading ISOs or setting up virtual machines, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://distrosea.com&#34;&gt;DistroSea&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; lets you dive in instantly, right from your browser.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-what-is-distrosea&#34;&gt;1. What Is DistroSea?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DistroSea is a free web-based platform that lets you launch and interact with over 60 Linux and BSD distributions directly in your browser, no installation needed. From mainstream distros like Ubuntu, Fedora, and Debian to niche options like Void, DragonFlyBSD, and Haiku, there’s something for every user.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Thoughtful Guide to X11 Desktop Environments</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-thoughtful-guide-to-x11/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 07:35:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-thoughtful-guide-to-x11/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving world of Linux desktop environments, there&amp;rsquo;s been a clear trend: &lt;strong&gt;Wayland&lt;/strong&gt; is growing. It&amp;rsquo;s sleek, modern, and promises a more secure and efficient future. But for many of us, &lt;strong&gt;Xorg (X11)&lt;/strong&gt; still represents stability, flexibility, and control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re on older hardware, running highly configurable window managers, or just appreciate the tried-and-true reliability of X11, this post is for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s explore the wide variety of &lt;strong&gt;Xorg-based desktop environments&lt;/strong&gt; that continue to thrive, not as resistance to change, but as a celebration of &lt;em&gt;freedom of choice&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a System Service Manager: A Personal Perspective</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/system-service-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:25:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/system-service-managers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to system service managers on Linux, such as systemd, OpenRC, runit, SysVinit, and others, the conversation can quickly turn into a debate. Each has its merits, its history, and its dedicated user base. But for most people using Linux on a desktop or laptop, the differences between them often fade quietly into the background.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At their core, service managers are responsible for initializing the system, managing background services (daemons), handling dependencies, logging, and shutting down gracefully. On servers, where stability, fine-grained control, and predictability are essential, choosing the right init system can be a high-stakes decision. Administrators often require transparency, auditability, and exact behavior, especially in high-availability or containerized environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Derivative of a Derivative Might Not Be the Best Choice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/derivative-of-a-derivative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 07:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/derivative-of-a-derivative/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When it comes to choosing a Linux distribution, the options can feel overwhelming. From the giants like Arch, Fedora, OpenSuse and Ubuntu, to the more niche derivatives that branch off these powerhouses, there’s a flavor for just about everyone. But what happens when you venture beyond a first-layer derivative to a derivative of a derivative? While it might seem harmless, this extra step away from the “source” can sometimes create unforeseen challenges that are worth considering before you commit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
