<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vancity Vanlife on d:tour</title>
    <link>https://furycd001.github.io/tags/vancity-vanlife/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vancity Vanlife on d:tour</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:43:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://furycd001.github.io/tags/vancity-vanlife/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cruz and the Mud Puddle</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/cruz-and-the-mud-puddle/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 07:43:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/cruz-and-the-mud-puddle/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the heart of the sprawling wilderness, there lived a charming bulldog named Cruz. Cruz was no ordinary bulldog; he was an intrepid explorer with a heart full of adventure. He traveled the country in a cozy, colorful van with his owner, Chrome. Chrome was a free spirit with a love for the open road, and together, they explored every nook and cranny of the beautiful landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One crisp morning, Cruz and Chrome arrived at a picturesque campground nestled among towering pine trees and shimmering lakes. Eager to stretch his legs, Cruz carefully walked down the steps that Chrome had set out at the side of the van, his tail wagging furiously. Chrome smiled, watching his loyal companion sniff around with boundless curiosity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chromes Fruity Fiasco</title>
      <link>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/chromes-fruity-fiasco/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:02:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://furycd001.github.io/posts/chromes-fruity-fiasco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chrome wandered through the bustling market, eyeing the vibrant display of fruit. He picked up a ripe mango, its sweet aroma mingling with the scent of nearby oranges and strawberries. As he bit into the juicy flesh, Chrome couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but smile, savoring the burst of tropical flavor that transported him to a sunny paradise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chrome tripped over a rogue pineapple and landed face-first in a pile of watermelons. &amp;ldquo;Well, at least I&amp;rsquo;m getting my daily fruit intake,&amp;rdquo; he muttered, spitting out seeds and trying to regain his dignity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
